// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does C-ASBA stands for?",
    answer: "Centralized Application for ASBA based issuance",
    options: [
	      "Centralized Application for ASBA based issuance",
      "Controlled Application Supported by Bulk Account",
      "Centralized Accounts Supported by Blocked Account",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who is a Beneficial Owner (BO) regarding DEMAT account?",
    answer: "DEMAT account holder",
    options: [
      "Bank who opens the DEMAT account",
      "Capital who owns the DEMAT account of customer",
      "DEMAT account holder",
      "Both 1 & 2 are correct"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What are the sources of dirty/black money?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
		"Human trafficking, Extortion",
      "Smuggling, Tax Evasion",
           "None of the above",
		   
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Consortium financing is defined as:",
    answer: "Financing a project by multiple banks",
    options: [
      "Financing a project by a single bank",
      "Financing a project by multiple banks",
      "None of the above",
		   
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Fixed deposits are:",
    answer: "Repayable after Maturity",
    options: [
	
      "Repayable on demand",
      "Repayable after Maturity",
      "Non repayable",
      "Negotiable"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Cheque payment/ transfer is not honored if:",
   answer: "All of the above",
 options: [
      "Pen ink differs",
     "Writing differs",
     "Cheque is issued 6 months before",
     "All of the above"
   ]
 },
 {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A minor account is converted into the major account if the account holder attains:",
   answer: "18 Years",
 options: [ 


      "16 Years",
     "18 Years",
     "17 Years",
     "15 Years"
   ]
 },
 {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is IPS?",
   answer: "Inter Bank Payment System",
 options: [

      "Inter Branch Payment System",
     "Inter Office Payment System",
     "Inter Bank Payment System",
     "Inter Bank Process System"
   ]
 },
 {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A cheque issued by Bank is valid for",
   answer: "6 months from the issue date",
 options: [
      "1 month from the issue date",
     "15 days from the issue date",
     "3 months from the issue date",
     "6 months from the issue date"
   ]
 },
 {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is not directly controlled by NRB?",
   answer: "Base Rate",
 options: [

      "CRR",
     "CAR",
     "Base Rate",
     "Bank Rate"
   ]
 },
 {
    numb: 11,
    question: "A cheque book can be issued in following accounts:",
   answer: "Saving account",
 options: [

      "Saving account",
     "Fixed deposit account",
     "Call account",
     "All of the above"
   ]
 },
 {
    numb: 12,
    question: "A party who issued the cheque is called as:",
   answer: "Drawer",
 options: [

      "Payee",
     "Drawee",
     "Drawer",
     "None of the above"
   ]
 },
 {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Thumb impression of the customer is mandatory to open the account of:",
   answer: "All of the above",
 options: [
      "Illiterate person",
     "Literate person",
     "None of the above",
     "All of the above"
   ]
 },
 {
    numb: 14,
    question: "A shell entity",
   answer: "Both A and B",
 options: [
      "Has no physical presence in the country in which it is incorporated",
     "Has no fixed assets or does not have active business operation",
	 "Is an unregistered entity",
	 "Both A and B"
  
   ]
 },
 {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is the full form of FIU in Nepal?",
   answer: "Financial Information Unit",
 options: [


      "Financial Intelligence Unit",
     "Financial Information Unit",
     "Full Investigation Unit",
     "Further Investigation Unit"
   ]
 },
 {
    numb: 16,
    question: "A PEP who no longer holds a prominent public position from last â€¦ years is not a PEP:",
   answer: "5 years",
 options: [
      "1 year",
     "2 years",
     "5 years",
     "7 years"
   ]
 },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Tax rate applicable on interest payment to individual is:",
   answer: "5.00%",
 options: [


      "10.00%",
     "5.00%",
     "25.00%",
     "15.00%"
   ]
 },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Current Account is terminated into dormant status if the account is not operated for:",
   answer: "6 months",
 options: [

      "12 months",
     "36 months",
     "9 months",
     "6 months"
   ]
 },
  {
    numb: 19,
   question: "Saving Account is terminated into dormant status if the account is not operated for:",
   answer: "36 months",
 options: [

      "12 months",
     "36 months",
     "9 months",
     "6 months"
   ]
 },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Account review frequency for High Risk Account is:",
   answer: "1 year",
 options: [

      "1 year",
     "2 years",
     "3 years",
     "4 years"
   ]
 },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
 
];